Finding Aid for the Ephraim Sales Collection of Tapes and Transcripts of Interviews by Roy Newquist LSC.1494
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Toynbee, Arnold (Writer)., 71 (Box 6)
  - Arnold Toynbee, undated; yrlsc1494_006_071a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:32:57) (Box 6, Case 71)
  - Arnold Toynbee, undated; yrlsc1494_006_071b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:03:19) (Box 6, Case 71)
- Toynbee, Arnold (Writer) -- Transcript of Tape no.71., (26pp.) (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Tracy, Spencer (Actor)
  See: Hepburn, Katherine
- Trilling, Diana (Writer). -- Transcript., 1964 March; (13pp.) (Box 18, Folder 20)
- Van Paassen, Pierre (Writer)., 164 (Box 12)
  - Pierre van Paassen, undated; yrlsc1494_012_164a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:24:35) (Box 12, Case 164)
  - Pierre van Paassen, undated; yrlsc1494_012_164b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:33:05) (Box 12, Case 164)
- Wagner, Robert (Actor) -- Transcript., (8pp.) (Box 18, Folder 23)
- Wagner, Robert (Actor)., 113 (Box 9)
  - Malachi Throne, Robert Wagner, undated; yrlsc1494_009_113; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:59:11) (Box 9, Case 113)
- Wagner, Robert (Actor)., 134 (Box 10)
- Wallace, Irving (Writer) -- Transcript., (9pp.) (Box 18, Folder 21)
- Wallach, Eli (Actor)., 118 (Box 9)
  - Eli Wallach, Doris Day, undated; yrlsc1494_009_118a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:49:29) (Box 9, Case 118)
  - Eli Wallach, Doris Day, undated; yrlsc1494_009_118b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:47:37) (Box 9, Case 118)
- Waller, Les (Writer). -- Transcript., 1963 September; (9pp.) (Box 18, Folder 22)
- Warren, Robert Penn (Writer)., 52 (Box 4)
  - Robert Penn Warren, undated; yrlsc1494_004_052a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:52:16) (Box 4, Case 52)
  - Robert Penn Warren, undated; yrlsc1494_004_052b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:48:06) (Box 4, Case 52)
- Warren, Robert Penn (Writer)., 135 (Box 10)
- Wayne, John (Actor)., 83 (Box 6)
  - John Wayne, Paul Newman, Katharine Ross, undated; yrlsc1494_006_083a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:52:18) (Box 6, Case 83)
  - John Wayne, Paul Newman, Katharine Ross, undated; yrlsc1494_006_083b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:53:28) (Box 6, Case 83)
    Content Note: Newquist recaps his interview with John Wayne at beginning of recording
- Weidman, Jerome (Writer)., 8 (Box 1)
  - Jerome Weidman, undated; yrlsc1494_001_008; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:32:07) (Box 1, Case 8)
- Weiss, David (Writer) -- Transcript., (10pp.) (Box 18, Folder 24)
- Welch, Raquel (Actress) -- Transcript., (5pp.) (Box 18, Folder 26)
- Welch, Raquel (Actress)., 112 (Box 8)
  - Raquel Welch, Allen Drury, undated; yrlsc1494_008_112a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:48:57) (Box 8, Case 112)
  - Raquel Welch, Allen Drury, undated; yrlsc1494_008_112b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:48:57) (Box 8, Case 112)
- Welch, Raquel (Actress) -- Transcript of Tape no.112., (20pp.) (Box 18, Folder 25)
- Wells, Leon (Writer). -- Transcript., 1963 September; (7pp.) (Box 18, Folder 27)
- West, Morris L. (Writer)., 22 (Box 2)
  - Counterpoint: Morris L. West, Counterpoint: Gabriel Fielding, 1964 March 20; yrlsc1494_002_022; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:19:21) (Box 2, Case 22)
- Who's afraid of Virginia Woolf? (Box 20, Folder 1-38)
  - Burton, Richard -- Transcript., (32pp.) (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Burton, Richard. IX -- Transcript., (12pp.) (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Cameos -- Transcript., (8pp.) (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Combs, Carol -- Transcript., (4pp.) (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Dennis, Sandy -- Transcript., (17pp.) (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Dennis, Sandy -- Transcript., (17pp.) (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Drafts of book about -- Transcript., (13pp.) (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Flanagan, Agnes -- Transcript., (3pp.) (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Index to breakdown -- Transcript., (36pp.) (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Lehman, Ernest -- Transcript., (7pp.) (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Lehman, Ernest -- Transcript., (13pp.) (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Lehman, Ernest -- Transcript., (30pp.) (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Lehman, Ernest -- Transcript., (10pp.) (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Lehman, Ernest. IX -- Transcript., (6pp.) (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Lehman, Ernest -- Transcript., (Some holograph, 23pp.) (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Lehman, Ernest. VI[I]., (23pp.) (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Lehman, Ernest. XII -- Transcript., (15pp.) (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Lehman, Ernest. VI -- Transcript., (12pp.) (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Nichols, Mike -- Transcript., (11pp.) (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Nichols, Mike -- Transcript., (3pp.) (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Nichols, Mike -- Transcript., (12pp.) (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Nichols, Mike -- Transcript., (10pp.) (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Nichols, Mike. XI -- Transcript., (12pp.) (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Outline/draft of book about -- Transcript., (33pp.) (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Queries on manuscripts about -- Transcript., (1p.) (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Rebner, Meta -- Transcript., (6pp.) (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Script -- Transcript., (146pp.) (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Segal, George -- Transcript., (20pp.) (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Segal, George -- Transcript., (12pp.) (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Segal, George. XIV -- Transcript., (13pp.) (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Taylor, Elizabeth -- Transcript., (16pp.) (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Taylor, Elizabeth -- Transcript., (8pp.) (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Taylor, Elizabeth. VII -- Transcript., (8pp.) (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Untitled article by Newquist -- Transcript., (42pp.) (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - X -- Transcript., (23pp.) (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - XIV -- Transcript., (1p.) (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - XV -- Transcript., (4pp.) (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - XVI -- Transcript., (13pp.) (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf Part I, undated; yrlsc1494_001_002; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:20:50) (Box 1, Case 2)
  Content Note: Features interviews with Edward Albee, Elizabeth Taylor, Richard Burton, Sandy Dennis, George Segal
- Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf Part II, undated; yrlsc1494_002_024; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:02:36) (Box 2, Case 24)
- Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf? Part III, undated; yrlsc1494_011_154a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:48:47) (Box 11, Case 154)
  Content Note: features conversation with script supervisor, Meta Rebner and hairstylist, Agnes Flanagan regarding their work on "Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf?"
- Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf? Part III, undated; yrlsc1494_011_154b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:28:07) (Box 11, Case 154)
- Wodehouse, P.G. (Writer). -- Transcript., 1965 January; (14pp.) (Box 18, Folder 29)
- Yarborough, Glenn (Singer)., 54 (Box 4)
  - Glenn Yarbrough, undated; yrlsc1494_004_054a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:32:28) (Box 4, Case 54)
  - Glenn Yarbrough, undated; yrlsc1494_004_054b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:32:31) (Box 4, Case 54)
- Yarborough, Glenn (Singer)., 61 (Box 5)
  - Glenn Yarbrough, undated; yrlsc1494_005_061a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:32:31) (Box 5, Case 61)
  - Glenn Yarbrough, undated; yrlsc1494_005_061b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:32:31) (Box 5, Case 61)
- Yarborough, Glenn (Singer) -- Transcript of Tape no.61., (45pp.) (Box 18, Folder 29)
- Young, Marguerite (Writer)., 160 (Box 11)
  - Marguerite Young, undated; yrlsc1494_011_160a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:24:06) (Box 11, Case 160)
  - Marguerite Young, undated; yrlsc1494_011_160b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:24:06) (Box 11, Case 160)
- Young, Marguerite (Writer) -- Transcript of Tape no.160., (32pp.) (Box 18, Folder 30)
- Young, Marguerite (Writer)., 169 (Box 12)
  - Marguerite Young, undated; yrlsc1494_012_169a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:20:17) (Box 12, Case 169)
  - Marguerite Young, undated; yrlsc1494_012_169b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:24:29) (Box 12, Case 169)
- Zolotow, Maurice (Writer)., 158 (Box 11)
  - George Peppard, Maurice Zolotow, undated; yrlsc1494_011_158a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:35:04); Condition Note: buzz throughout recording (Box 11, Case 158)
  - George Peppard, Maurice Zolotow, undated; yrlsc1494_011_158b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:24:49) (Box 11, Case 158)